DILLON COUCHOIS

909 910 9081

dcouchois@gmail.com

2569 La Salle Pointe Chino Hills CA 91709

Summary

Front-End Web Developer with a background in Photography and Design with a keen eye for detail. Recently received a certificate in Full Stack Development from the University of California Irvine in JavaScript, CSS, React.js and responsive web design. My aim is to bring a dynamic experience to each user accompanied by modern and compelling design.

Education

California State University Fullerton 2006 - 2012 Graduated with a Fine Arts Degree in Creative Photography

University Of California Irvine Bootcamp Program for Full Stack Web Development

Experience

Freelance Photo Assisting / Digital Technician 2017 - present

- Setup of multiple light systems to achieve desired look
- Coordination with multiple teams to ensure highest quality of imagery
- Changing of light setups on the fly to incorporate new ideas
- Organization and allocation of photos
- Color editing and correction of photographs to be batched out
- Syncing of multiple drives to be prepped for delivery to clients

Mullerphoto Inc. / Studio Manager 2015 - 2018

- Backing up, restoring, and setting up new macintosh based computers and smart phones
- Management, cataloging, and administration of over 200-terabytes of photo and video data crucial to the company's intellectual property
- Setup and maintenance of multiple printer systems accompanied with correct icc and other color profiles
- Backing up, restoring and setting up new hard drives
- Email and calendar synchronization between multiple platforms

Velem Post Production (Retouching) 2018

- Using Photoshop to clean skin, clothes, and backgrounds
- Composited multiple images/parts of images together to create the correct look for client
- Insured consistency between photographs to match clients needs

Skills

HTML, CSS, REACT.JS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, NodeJS, MySql, MongoDB, JQuery, Express, JSON, Sourcetree, Microsoft Office, MacOS, Outlook, CaptureOne, PhotoshopCC